Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 10 and District 10 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 10 Locals, 2.
  - Local 1421
    - Local 1421 Miscellaneous, 1937-1941 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Proposed Agreement Regarding Phelps Dodge, November 9, 1937; 2.
      - William Mitchell to Wiley Brown Regarding Phelps Dodge Contract, November 30, 1937; 3.
      - Verne Kennedy to H.W. Dunhan Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation, November 7, 1938; 4.
      - Shop Committee Management Minutes Regarding Columbia Records Firings with Affidavits, October 26, 1939; 5.
      - Letter to P.E. Crowley Regarding Columbia Records and Firings, October 28, 1939; 6.
      - Ballot Regarding Officers, January 1940; 7.
      - S.R. Robin to Local 1421 Regarding Dura Contract and Staff Members, August 20, 1940; 8.
      - Wendell Phillips to Matles Regarding Negotiation, February 14, 1941; 9.
      - GE Work Rules, February 1941; 10.
    - Local 1421 Miscellaneous, 1941-46 (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Wendell Phillips to Julius Emspak Regarding Military Training with March 6, 1941, Phillips Letter to Douglas Wilson, 1.
      - Carl Brant to James Matles Regarding Reliable Organization, October 2, 1941; 2.
      - Grayson Heat Control Weekly Shift Report, January 1942; 3.
      - E.L. Daggett to A.N. Towson Regarding Organization, November 12, 1942; 4.
      - Phelps Dodge Proposed Agreement, 1942; 5.
      - George Dodson to Emspak Regarding GE Ontario, April 1, 1943; 6.
      - Emspak to Dodson Regarding GE Contract, April 13, 1943; 7.
      - Leo Turner to Emspak Regarding Zinsmeyer Organization, April 26, 1943; 8.
      - Turner to Matles Regarding Staff Members, Contracts, and Organization, May 28, 1943; 9.
      - Turner to Emspak Regarding Cannon Organization and Local 1013, June 4, 1943; 10.
      - William Sentner to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, January 8, 1945; 11.
      - Carl Brant to Joseph Dermody Regarding Columbia and RCA Negotiations, September 29, 1945; 12.
      - Termination of Strike Regarding Sterling Motors, March 27, 1946; 13.
    - Local 1421 Miscellaneous, 1947-1952 (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - James Marsh to James Matles Regarding Taft Hartley with Organizing Without the National Labor Relations Board Leaflet, September 23, 1947; 1.
      - Special Executive Board Meeting Minutes Regarding Strike, April 13, 1948; 2.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement Regarding Domestic Thermostat, April 20, 1948; 3.
      - William Elconin to Matles Regarding Allied Records and Loyalty Oath with Loyalty Pledge and May 14, 1948, Local 1421 Letter to Allied Records, May 26, 1948; 4.
      - Reorganization Proposals for Local 1421, 1948; 5.
      - Jacob Soloman to UE Regarding Wages and Publicity, April 5, 1951; 6.
      - Julius Emspak to George Gibbs Regarding Local 1425, September 11, 1952; 7.
    - Local 1421 Los Angeles Phelps Dodge and Radio, 1979-1986 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Local 1421 Legislative Committee and Political Action, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Local 1421 Strikes, Subsidies and Other Monies, 1973-1982 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Local 1421 Representation Grievances with Photographs, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Local 1421 Siliconix, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Local 1421 Special Financial, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Local 1421 Western Insulated Wire Strike, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Local 1421 American Brake Shoe Strike, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Local 1421 United Superior Records, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Local 1421 Correspondence, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Local 1421 Agreement with Local 700 Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Local 1421 Los Angeles, CA, 1956-1967 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Local 1421 Per-Leon Torchinsky Grievance, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Local 1425
    - Local 1425 Officers Lists, December 25, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Local 1425 Incoming Correspondence, 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 76)
      - Julius Emspak to A.R. Moreton Regarding General Cable Organization, June 17, 1937; 1.
      - Moreton to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, November 3, 1937; 2.
      - W.E. Murphy to James Carey Regarding Legislation, March 19, 1938; 3.
      - Murphy to William Mitchell Regarding Wages, April 2, 1938; 4.
      - Murphy to Mitchell Regarding Contracts and Organization, April 2, 1938; 5.
      - Murphy to Mitchell Regarding Vacations and General Cable Negotiation, May 27, 1938; 6.
    - Local 1425 Report of Financial Secretary, May-December 1937 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Local 1425 Per Capita Report, January-May 1938 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Local 1425 Organization, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 79)
      - A.R. Moreton to James Carey, March 27, 1937; 1.
      - Moreton to Julius Emspak, March 29, 1937; 2.
      - Carey to Moreton, April 12, 1937; 3.
      - Emspak to Moreton, April 8, 1937; 4.
  - Local 1426
    - Local 1426 Incoming Correspondence, N.V. Bramley to Julius Emspak Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, September 10, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Local 1426 Notices of Delinquency and Suspension, May 1937-January 1938 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Local 1426 Report of Financial Secretary, May-July 1937 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Local 1426 Per Capita Reports, August 1937-May 1938 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Local 1426 Correspondence and Wage Rates, 1938, undated (Box 5, Folder 85)
      - Wages Rates, n.d.; 1.
      - Leo Turner to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, May 10, 1938; 2.